CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME: Ahmed Mohamed Hassan

D.O.B: 1994

ADDRESS: Kenya, Nairobi, Eastleigtht

MARITAL STATUS: Single

PHONE NO: +254740333023

EMAIL: ahmedhassanbicir.aa98@gmail.com

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sept 2017 to date: JOMO KENYATTA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE

AND TECHNOLOGY

2012-2015: Green-light secondary school

January 2016-june 2016:Do%n bosco Technical Institute

2010-2011: Cambella Primary School

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

January 2021-present.a tutor at Samaha Technologies.teaching front end(html5,css3,javascript,react,redux,axios and saga)

September 2020- November 2020.taugh Python programming language at Solidarity Initiative For Refugees in kakuma camp.

Worked as interpreter from june 2018-november 2019 at Refugee affairs secretariat(RAS).

June 2016-august 2017: lutheran world federation federation(LWF), peacebuilding unit, case worker.

January 2016-may2017 Worked as a teacher in Lokitang primary school

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- Being promoted as case worker supervisor
- Promoted peace at my location
- Taught young children the moral values of peace

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am hard working and dedicated person who has a great passion for software engineering, can work under pressure and can be relied upon to excel in any given role. I am therefore ready to improve my experience at the time I am in your locality.

I am self driven, motivated and passionate about coding.

TRAININGS PARTICIPATED

- MIT App inventor training for android
- Wordpress and jumla training
- Basic counseling
- Training of trainers in Mediation and conflict resolution
- Teachers trainings
- Violence prevention and peace promotion
- Community mobilization & Peace building
- Sexual Gender Based Violence
- Basic computer trainings (MS Word, Office, Excel, Power point,ms access)

LANGUAGES

- English
- Somali
- Kiswahili

REFEREES

- 1. Mohamed Abdi: Ceo At Samaha Technologies, +254726549879
- 2. Joseph kasi :center admin of solidarity initiative for refugees
- 3. patric LWF head of peacebuilding
- 4. john kodi, LWF deputy head teacher of Lokitaung primary school